all right it's tuesday March 31st 2015
好吧，它是2015年3月31日星期二
and here are the stories were covering
以下是故事的内容
this week confidential information about
本周机密信息
31 of the world leaders were
世界领导人中 有 31位 是
accidentally emailed to the asian cup
不小心通过电子邮件发送到了亚洲杯
organizers in australia ATR the big
组织者在 澳大利亚ATR大
brother of isps future shop closed all
isps未来商店的兄弟全部关闭
its canadian stores on sunday to the
它的加拿大商店周日到
surprise of even their staff a brand new
甚至他们的员工一个全新的惊喜
high-end modular gaming mouse is
高端模块化游戏鼠标是
available for pre-order through
可用于预购
crowdfunding and its unique design will
众筹及其独特的设计意愿
put it on any serious gamers shopping
把它放在任何严肃的玩家购物上
list and legacy Roku devices are about
列表和传统的Roku设备是关于
to be deprecated and it may be time to
被弃用， 可能是时候了
upgrade these stories are coming right
升级这些 故事是正确的
up don't go anywhere thanks Sasha and
起来不要去任何地方，谢谢Sasha和
tonight we're talking a lot about
今晚我们谈的很多
backups and one of the things that
备份和其中一件事
dreamhost provides for you is a 50 gig
dreamhost为你提供50演出
backup storage space on their servers
备份服务器上的存储空间
for only seventy dollars a year you're
你一年只需要七十美元
going to get carbon neutral lamp hosting
将获得碳中性灯托管
on Linux of course you're going to get a
在Linux上当然你会 得到一个
free domain name registration unlimited
免费域名注册无限制
storage space for your website as well
您网站的存储空间
as be able to host an unlimited number
因为能够容纳无限数量
of of websites and email accounts plus
网站和电子邮件帐户加
they throw in that 50 gigs of personal
他们投入了50场演出
backup storage space go to cat five dot
备份存储空间转到cat五点
TV / dreamhost and use the coupon code
TV / dreamhost并使用优惠券代码
cat five TV to sign up today back to the
猫五电视今天报名回来了
newsroom here Sasha I'm Sasha drew
新闻室在这里Sasha我是Sasha画的
Madison here the top stories from the
麦迪逊来自这里的头条新闻
category 5 TV news room
5类电视新闻室
the passport numbers and visa details of
护照号码和签证详情
31 world leaders were accidentally
31名世界领导人意外发生
emailed to the organizers of the asian
通过电子邮件发送给亚洲组织者
cup in australia before the g20 summit
在G20峰会前的澳大利亚杯
in Brisbane in November those affected
11月在布里斯班受影响
included US President Barack Obama and
包括美国总统巴拉克奥巴马和
German Chancellor Angela Merkel Angela
德国总理安吉拉默克尔安吉拉
Merkel sir a worker at the Australian
默克尔先生是 澳大利亚的 一名工人
Department of Immigration sent the list
移民局发送了这份名单
by mistake the best by mistake the
错误的最好是错误的
message included the 31 world leaders
消息包括31位世界领导人
dates of birth but not the personal
出生日期但不是个人日期
addresses and other contact details just
地址和其他联系方式
visa and passport information the bridge
签证和护照信息的桥梁
was said to be the result of human error
据说是人为错误的结果
with the sender forgetting to check the
与发件人忘记检查
autofill functions in Microsoft Outlook
Microsoft Outlook中的自动填充功能
email service before hitting send
点击发送前的电子邮件服务
according to the officer both the sender
根据官员和发件人的说法
of the email and the recipient had
电子邮件和收件人的
deleted it within 10 minutes of it being
在它出现的10分钟内将其删除
sent and the asian cup football
发送和亚洲杯足球
tournament organizers said they did not
比赛组织者表示他们没有
believe the email was accessible or
相信电子邮件是可访问的或
stored on their servers my god the
存储在他们的服务器上我的上帝
department decided there was no need to
部门决定没有 必要
alert the g20 attendees clearly
清楚地提醒g20与会者
indicating that they don't understand
表明他们不理解
how email works Wow Robbie so will you
电子邮件如何工作哇罗比你也会这样
explain how email works yeah sure I'd be
解释电子邮件是如何工作的，确定我会
happy to okay for all of you who are
高兴 好所有 你们 谁
dealing with government personal
处理政府个人问题
information secret here's my secret my
信息秘密在这里是我的秘密我的
pens died doesn't happy there you go so
钢笔死了不高兴你去那么
my secret it says sec or sacker but sec
我的秘密是说秒或者麻烦但是秒
there you go i can pass this to you
你去， 我可以把它传给你
right there's an email it's it's
就在那里有一封电子邮件就是这样
perfectly visible to anyone who is
任何人都能看到
looking for that email as it goes
寻找 那封电子邮件
through the servers it gets to you and
通过它到达你的服务器
you might shred it or rip it up or burn
你可能会撕碎它或将其撕碎或燃烧
it or whatever but while it's in transit
它或其他任何东西， 但它在运输途中
it's plain text do you know how the
这是纯文本你知道吗？
internet works like it's the World Wide
互联网的工作方式就像是全世界的
Web you've got a whole bunch of little
网络你有一大堆
nodes and they're all connected together
节点和它们都连接在一起
and when I sent an email to you Sasha it
当我发给你Sasha的电子邮件时
doesn't go to you it goes to my isp
不去找你它去了我的isp
might be looking well first it goes
可能会寻找好它先
through the hotel where I'm connected to
穿过我所连接的酒店
the Wi-Fi then it goes to the ISP then
Wi-Fi然后它去ISP
it goes to every little computer along
它随便进入每一台小电脑
the way and through all these computers
通过所有这些计算机的方式
to get to the recipient mm-hmm and who's
到达收件人mm-hmm和谁
to say one of those computers isn't
说其中一台电脑不是
effective infected with a botnet or an
有效感染僵尸网络或僵尸网络
email sniffer or maybe there is actually
电子邮件嗅探器或者实际上可能存在
a malicious person on the other end
另一端是恶意的人
watching email as it passes through and
看电子邮件，因为它通过和
watching for confidential records wasn't
看机密记录不是
it you Robbie that said that sending an
你罗比那说 发送一个
email is the same as sending a postcard
电子邮件与发送明信片相同
was it I feel like that's something you
是不是我觉得那就是你
would say it sounds like a really great
会说这听起来真的很棒
quote so i will accept that as my own
引用所以我会接受这个作为我自己的
yes I think that that's really really
是的我觉得 那 真的很棒
true i mean that that may have been
我的意思是， 这可能是
somebody in the chat room I don't know
聊天室里有人我不 知道
if I've ever spoken those words but
如果我说过这些话，但是
that's that's a great example postcard
这就是明信片的一个很好的例子
how do you know that it got to my postal
你怎么知道它到了我的邮政
box without someone else reading it I
没有别人看过它的盒子我
guarantee you probably a lot of people
保证你可能很多人
read it if it looked interesting on the
阅读它，如果它看起来很有趣
on the cover all right absolutely that's
在封面上绝对是那样的
email email is plain text and I think
电子邮件是纯文本，我想
and you can read about it in my blog
你可以在我的博客中阅读它
bald nerd com actually posted a recent
秃头书呆子com最近发布了一个
article about the fact that we get
关于我们得到的事实的文章
deceived thinking that email is secure
欺骗性地认为电子邮件是安全的
because we've got secure authentication
因为我们有安全的身份验证
to connect to our server or because when
连接到我们的服务器或因为什么时候
we bring up Gmail it's a secure website
我们将Gmail打造成一个安全的网站
and so we think oh this is secure oh
所以我们认为哦这是安全的哦
nice gmail is secure well the instant i
好的Gmail很快就能安全了
press send it leaves Gmail which is a
按发送它离开Gmail这是一个
secure connection so my connection to
所以我的连接安全连接
gmail is secure during that transaction
gmail在该交易期间是安全的
but as soon as i hit send it goes out in
但是当我点击发送它就会消失
plain text anywhere in the world you
世界上任何地方的纯文本你
don't know nobody knows it just tunnels
不知道没有人知道它只是隧道
its way finally finding itself at the
它终于找到了自己的方式
recipient and it is not a transaction
收件人，这不是交易
where it absolutely guaranteed Lee gets
它绝对保证李得到的地方
deleted from every server it goes
它从每个服务器中删除
through so what they're saying is
通过他们所说的是
because they didn't back it up they just
因为他们没有支持它们
assume it's gone forever so what
假设它已经永远消失 了
happened they deleted it within 10
发生了他们在10内删除了它
minutes gone forever it doesn't work
分钟一去不复返这是行不通的
that way folks oh my goodness Wow all
伙计们哦，我的天哪哇
right if you have AT&amp;T s gigabit
对，如果你有AT＆T的千兆位
internet service and wonder why it seems
互联网服务，并想知道为什么
so affordable here
在这里很实惠
the reason AT&amp;T is boosting profits by
AT＆T提高利润的原因
rerouting all your web browsing to an
将您的所有网页浏览重新路由到
in-house traffic scanning platform
内部交通扫描平台
analyzing your internet habits then
然后分析你的网络习惯
using the results to deliver
使用结果来传递
personalized ads to the websites you
个性化广告到您的网站
visit email to your inbox and junk mail
访问收件箱和垃圾邮件的电子邮件
to your front door wait Sasha yes not to
到你的前门等Sasha是的不是
revert back to a previous story but does
恢复到以前的故事，但确实如此
that mean that they could also be
这意味着他们也可以
watching email ah hypothetical exactly
看电子邮件啊假设完全正确
if let's say the organizers of this
如果让我们说这个的组织者
summit had logged on to AT&amp;T and then
峰会已经登陆AT＆T然后
sent the email right then they would
发送电子邮件然后他们会
have been 80 would have President
已经80岁就会有总统
Obama's password or passport sorry
奥巴马的密码或护照 对不起
passport number and you know visa for
护照号码，你知道签证
any possibility yeah it's crazy all
任何可能性，是的，这一切都很疯狂
right in a few select areas including
在几个选定的领域，包括
Austin Texas and Kansas City Missouri
奥斯汀德克萨斯州和堪萨斯城 密苏里州
places where AT&amp;T competes against the
AT＆T与之竞争的地方
seventy dollar per month Google Fiber
每月七十美元谷歌光纤
mahvel offers its own seventy dollar per
mahvel每人提供七十美元
month gigapower fiber to the home
月gigapower 光纤到家
internet access but signing up for the
互联网接入，但报名参加
deal also ops customers into a tease
交易也让客户开玩笑
internet preferences program which gives
互联网偏好计划给出
the company permission to examine each
公司允许检查每个
customer's web traffic in exchange for a
客户的网站流量换来了
price that matches Google's AT&amp;T says
价格与谷歌的AT＆T相匹配
internet preferences tracked the web
互联网偏好跟踪 网络
pages you visit the time you spend on
您访问的 页面 花费的时间
each the links are ads you see and
每个链接都是您看到的广告
follow and the search terms you enter
按照您输入的搜索字词
this helps AT&amp;T serve ads targeted to
这有助于AT＆T投放定位广告
each user based on that person's
每个用户都是基于那个人的
interests and advertisers are willing to
兴趣和广告商愿意
pay more when they know their ads will
当他们知道自己的广告时会 付出 更多
be shown to the people most likely to be
向最有可能成为的人展示
interested in their products that scares
对他们惊恐的产品感兴趣
me it's just like the time you spend on
我就像你花的时间一样
each webpage so they can tell if you you
每个网页，以便他们可以判断您是否
know just accidentally click that page
知道只是意外点击该页面
and then decide oh that's not where I
然后决定哦，那不是我的地方
want it to be sure yeah and then we even
希望它确定是的，然后我们甚至
use analytics data to know okay if you
如果你使用分析数据就可以了解
click on to our website we know if you
点击我们的网站我们知道你是否
watched 15 minutes of the show vs. 45
看了15分钟的节目 与45
minutes of the show and that makes this
节目的分钟， 这使得这一点
thing okay well then the first 15
好的，那么前15
minutes of the show is
节目的分钟是
valuable for advertisers for example and
例如对广告商有价值
so but we do it in a non-intrusive
所以我们这样做是非侵入性的
non-identifiable way like that it almost
几乎不可识别的方式
seems you're doing something and not to
好像你在做什么而不是做
point at 80 specifically but they're the
具体指向80，但他们是
ones in the news right now but it's
现在在新闻中，但它是
really coming down to are you only using
你真的 只是在使用
that data for advertising and really
广告的数据和真的
what does it come down to as far as the
到底是什么呢？
information that you're collecting right
您正在收集的信息
oh it's just scary to think that
哦，想到这一点真可怕
somebody else is watching like everybody
别人正在像大家一样看着
wants to have maintain privacy you're
我想保持你的隐私
giving it up because it seems too good
放弃，因为它似乎太好了
to be true cost wise it likely is once
要真正的成本，它可能只有一次
again it goes back to is your internet
再次回到你的互联网
connection really your internet
连接 真的是你的网络
connection who is watching who's
谁在看谁的联系
intercepting the data who's getting
拦截正在获取的数据
access to that ain't 18t they are
访问它不是18t
because AT&amp;T you can see almost
因为AT＆T几乎可以看到
everything you do online no matter what
无论如何，你在网上做的一切
websites you visit the company may be an
您访问该公司的网站可能是
even better position to serve targeted
更有利于有针对性地服务
ads than Facebook or Google while Google
广告比Facebook或谷歌而谷歌
apparently doesn't impose anything
显然没有强加任何东西
similar to internet preferences on its
类似于互联网的偏好
fiber internet the company's cable
光纤互联网公司的电缆
service is delivering targeted TV ads
服务提供有针对性的电视广告
based on its customers viewing history
基于其客户查看历史记录
so Google uses it in some ways as well
因此Google也会在某些方面使用它
sure they do yeah wow I just give me the
确定他们会这样做哇我只是给我了
heebie-jeebies I don't pick it I think
heebie-jeebies 我觉得 我不接受 它
with just because you bring up Google
只是因为你带来谷歌
Google is a search engine so I'm going
Google是一个搜索引擎，所以我要去
to their site and I'm using their
到他们的网站，我正在使用他们的
service and there's possibility that
服务，有可能
they're you know they're connected to
他们知道他们已经联系到了
other sites as well of course but when
其他网站当然， 但当然
you're going through your internet
你正在通过互联网
service provider they see everything not
服务提供商他们看不到一切
just what I search for or what website
正是我搜索的内容或网站
i'm on they see everything right well
我在他们看到一切正常
here's a thing I mean it just drives me
这是我的意思， 它只是 驱使我
bananas I know everybody is watching not
香蕉我知道每个人都在看
everybody but I know that I don't look
大家但是我知道我 不看
everybody my ego is huge everybody
每个人我的自我都是巨大的
everything I do but recently I bought my
我做的一切，但最近我买了我的
sister a throw cushion or throw pillow
妹妹扔垫或扔枕头
for her bridal shower ok so I searched a
为她的新娘送礼好，所以我搜索了一个
whole bunch on Amazon picked one I used
亚马逊上的一大堆选了一个我用的
the affiliate links thing wasn't a great
联盟链接的东西不是很好
five no problem
五没问题
but then later on I was google searching
但后来我在谷歌搜索
something and it was an ad with that
一些东西，这是一个广告
cushion right haha but here's the thing
坐垫哈哈，但这就是事情
I mean I know you're watching me but
我的意思是我知道你在 看着我
don't be so obvious about it it makes
它不会那么明显
sense though I'm from an advertising
感觉虽然我来自广告
perspective because if I look at
透视，因为如果我看
something it reminds me it's almost I
它提醒我几乎是我的东西
it's almost become a handy thing to know
知道它几乎成了一个方便的事情
that when I'm on any website amazon will
当我在亚马逊的任何网站上时都会
show me the stuff that I want but I
告诉我我想要的东西，但我
already bought it that's it y yeah i
已经买了它，是的， 是的，我
know that leasing nathan noted already
知道租赁nathan已经注意到了
made the purchase wait hounding me i
使购买等待追捕我我
don't want another pillow fix i do want
我不想要另一个枕头修理我想要的
another pillow actually they don't get
另一个枕头实际上他们没有得到
one okay us consumer electronics chain
一个好的消费电子产品链
best buy has announced that it is
最佳购买已经宣布它是
closing its canadian subsidiary future
关闭其加拿大子公司的未来
shop and converting 65 of its 131 stores
购物并转换其131家商店中的65家
into bestbuy outlets as a result of the
因为这个问题进入了最好的商店
move 500 full-time jobs in 1000
在 1000中移动500个全职工作
part-time jobs will go the retailer said
兼职工作将由零售商说
future shop canada's biggest electronics
未来店加拿大最大的电子产品
brand has been owned by bestbuy since
品牌自此以来一直由bestbuy所有
2001 after the changeover is completed
2001年转换完成后
best buy will have 192 Canadian stores
最好买的将有192家加拿大商店
analysts say the move will rationalize
分析师表示此举将合理化
best buys offer in Canada and get rid of
加拿大最好的购买和摆脱
duplication best buy in future shop
复制最好在未来的商店购买
outlets are often found in close
网点经常在附近找到
proximity they say I oh but this is just
接近他们说我哦，但这只是
heartbreaking for me because I have a
我心碎，因为我有一个
future shop I feel brand loyal to future
未来的商店我觉得品牌忠于未来
shop even though they're owned by best
虽然它们是最好的，但仍然是商店
buy I don't feel like royal to bestbuy
买我不觉得皇室好买
future shop is first and I remember
未来的商店是第一，我记得
growing up with it and and the the news
与它一起成长和新闻
tells us that they announced that
告诉我们他们宣布了这一点
they're shutting down they didn't really
他们正在关闭他们并没有真的
do it that way did they know I mean for
这样做他们知道我的意思
me to show up at work and be told sorry
我在 工作 中出现了 ，被告知对不起
no work today we're closed it's really
今天没有工作我们关闭了它真的
how it went down I certainly hope that
如何下降我当然希望如此
all the future shop employees are
所有未来的店员都是
offered positions in the new best buy
提供新的最佳购买头寸
stores but not all of them will be
商店但不是全部都是
converting over I guess you don't be
转换过来我想你不会
completely closed true enough i mean the
完全封闭真的，我的意思是
doors are closed and really there are a
门是关闭的，真的有一个
lot of future shops right next to best
很多未来的商店就在旁边
buy's right and i think that i thought
买对了， 我 想 我想
about it at the time and I thought okay
关于它当时，我认为没关系
at least unlike target these people are
至少与这些人的目标不同
going to get a severance I
我要分手了
hope because they're not milking out the
希望因为他们没有挤出来
time you know like it was I showed up to
你知道的时间就像我出现的那样
work that day and I'm laid off so I've
那天工作，我被解雇了，所以我
got a little bit of money at least
至少得到了一点点钱
coming my way for the next few weeks I
接下来的几个星期，我来了
hope that's how it went down but you
希望它是如何下降但你
don't really know you think I mean here
真的不知道你认为我的意思是在这里
I don't know what it's like anywhere
我不知道它在任何地方都是什么样的
else but here they have like one Tim
除此之外他们就像一个蒂姆
Hortons across the street from another
街对面的霍顿从另一个
two important yes and they have
两个重要的是，他们有
starbucks across the street from there
街对面的星巴克
like they have a like tons of which is
就像他们有类似的吨
really just a very expensive Tim Hortons
真的只是一个非常昂贵的蒂姆霍顿斯
right so if you have a future shop and a
如果你有一个未来的商店和一个
best buy in the same block and the
最好买 同一块和
parent company is best buy they're still
母公司最好买他们还是
making the money off of both of those
从这两方面赚钱
even though people have that's the
即使人们有这样的
society that we are in I don't want to
我们所在的社会我不想
have to go across the street they're
他们必须 穿过街道
profiting off their own competition of
获利过自己的竞争
the fruit that's what they I'm thinking
他们正在思考的水果
like if I don't want to shop at best buy
喜欢如果我 不想购物最好买
i'm gonna go to future shop yeah but
我要去未来的商店，但是
yeah like that's why for the win on that
是的，这就是为什么胜利的原因
now it's just gonna be best buy
现在它只是最好买
everywhere I'm gonna feel like I have no
到处都是我会觉得 我没有
choice and then I'll shop on amazon
选择然后我会在亚马逊购物
using our affiliate links exact I see
确切地说，使用我们的会员链接
where this is going life is could be a
生活在哪里可能 是一个
very good Wow a new style of high-end
非常好哇一种新的高端风格
gaming mouse is about to take the world
游戏鼠标即将走向世界
by storm it's called the James donkey
风暴它被称为詹姆斯驴
double-oh-seven mouse and it's made to
双七七鼠标，它的制作
be very customizable with magnetic parts
可以通过磁性部件进行定制
that snap on and off so gamers can build
随意拍摄，让游戏玩家可以建立
an ergonomic mouse that suits the way
符合人体工程学的鼠标
they play with an Ave go a 9800 chip
他们和Ave一起玩9800芯片
8400 DPI sensor and imran switch is
8400 DPI传感器和imran开关是
tested to 20 million clicks the double
测试到双倍的2000万次点击
07 is in a league with the best gaming
07年是最好的游戏联盟
mice out there with the new James donkey
与新詹姆斯驴在那里的老鼠
double-oh-seven you can easily remove
双哦七你可以轻松 删除
and replace magnetic components such as
并更换磁性元件，如
what Robbie Oh put me on the spot yeah
罗比哦当场把我当作是什么
well you think this is a neat idea a so
嗯，你认为这 是一个很好的想法
that you know are you don't need a
你知道的， 你不需要
screwdriver to take the pieces off you
螺丝刀取下你的碎片
don't need to unclip things it's just
不需要unclip的东西，它只是
it's super powers bag that's right that
这是超级大国包这是正确的
pull it in so you think if you're
把它拉进去让你想想你是不是
playing a flight simulator or something
玩飞行模拟器什么的
would it be cool to have
拥有它会很酷吗？
like that hook feature on your on your
就像你上的那个钩子功能一样
pinky right so that as you are you know
小拇指，这样你就知道了
working it has more of a flight
工作它有更多的飞行
simulator feel or take that off and put
模拟器的感觉或取消和放
on another component or actually adapt
在另一个组件上或实际适应
it to like how many variations can you
它喜欢你有多少变化
make this mouse all the components come
使这个鼠标成为所有组件
apart and you replace them with other
分开，你用其他替换它们
pieces do you have to buy all these
你需要购买所有这些
extra pieces I did think I can see i
额外的作品我认为 我能看到我
hope i don't know i would hope they
希望我不知道我希望他们
would come with the most but I feel like
会有最多，但我觉得
they wouldn't I feel like sasha has more
他们不 觉得sasha有更多
information for us you can't possibly a
给我们的信息你不可能
website link why it maybe we can find
网站链接为什么我们可以找到
out more information i want to know i
了解更多我想知道的信息
will say i love the name with the new
会说我喜欢新的名字
Jimmy's don't attorney yeah taxi with
吉米的律师不是出租车
the new James donkey double-oh-seven oh
新詹姆斯驴双哦七哦
wait I already said that sorry um where
等我说对不起你在哪里
was I oh I'm all along telling me
我是哦，我一直都在告诉我
rewound its goodness gracious it changes
重温它的善良，它的变化
the outward appearance of the mouse but
鼠标的外观但是
also the electronic functionality of the
也是电子的功能
switch this unique design makes up to 54
这种独特的开关设计最多可达54个
configurations possible the day for 50
配置可能是50天
40 configurations the James donkey team
詹姆斯驴队的 40个配置
are making the molds now and are well on
正在制造模具现在并且很好
their way to raising the funds for the
他们为筹集资金的方式
first production run for a limited time
首次生产运行时间有限
you can order the double oh seven for
你可以订购双哦七
just 41 dollars and both workers are
只有41美元，两个工人都是
also available that's an incredible deal
这也是一个令人难以置信的交易
so if you get all of the pieces for $41
所以， 如果 你以41美元的价格得到所有的碎片
wowzers visit our short link at cat5 TV
wowzers访问cat5 TV的短链接
/ double-oh-seven to support the
/ double-oh-seven支持
campaign and get your hands on this
活动并亲自动手
innovative high-end gaming mouse that's
创新的高端 游戏鼠标
good now I guess my only concern would
好现在我想我唯一关心的是
be the high-powered magnets they
是他们的高功率磁铁
wouldn't disturber I feel like straw
不会打扰我感觉像是稻草
your yeah this you don't want your tie
你的是啊你不想要领带
powered magnets too close to your you
动力磁铁太靠近你了
compare I when I didn't set it on your
比较我，当我没有把它设置在你的
hard drive thanks I it's yeah I mean
硬盘谢谢我，是的，我的意思是
these days things are not as
这些天事情并非如此
magnetically sensitive as they used to
像以前一样对磁感应敏感
be oh that's good yeah yeah it's it's
哦，那很好，是的，是的，是的
crazy and awesome and I want one I like
疯狂和令人敬畏，我想要一个我喜欢的
it yes
是的
for some time now older Roku streaming
一段时间以来现在更老的Roku流媒体
players those made before may 2011 have
那些在2011年之前制作的球员有
not been able to benefit from the many
没能从众多中受益
improvements that have been made to the
已经作出了改进
Roku OS this means customers with legacy
Roku OS这意味着拥有传统的客户
devices are not able to experience
设备无法体验
important new features that deliver the
重要的新功能，提供
great streaming experience Roku wants
Roku想要的流媒体体验
for its customers and soon they will be
对于它的客户而且他们很快就会成功
cutting off development for those
切断那些人的发展
devices entirely while consumers with
设备完全与消费者同在
legacy devices will continue to have
传统设备将继续拥有
access to channels that have already
访问已经存在的频道
launched on those devices going forward
在这些设备上推出
Roku will no longer launch any new
Roku将不再推出任何新产品
channels update existing channels issue
渠道更新现有渠道问题
firmware updates or provide developer
固件更新或提供开发人员
support for channels that run on these
支持在这些渠道上运行的渠道
older devices since this is the case
较旧的设备，因为这样的话
legacy Roku devices will soon be
传统的Roku设备即将推出
crippled since channel developers and
自渠道开发商以来一直瘫痪
content providers will have no way to
内容提供商将无法做到
make updates to their channel software
更新他们的频道软件
that said due to the nature of Roku's
这说是由于Roku的 性质
platform new content from channels still
来自渠道的平台新内容仍在
operating on legacy hardware will
在传统硬件上运行会
continue to be updated such as new
继续更新如新
episodes of category 5 TV however as
然而，类别5电视的剧集
services evolve and grow channels may
服务的发展和增长渠道可能会
break and no longer function current
休息， 不再是当前的功能
generation Roku players and Roku TV
一代Roku球员和Roku电视
models are not affected if you're using
如果您正在使用，模型不会受到影响
a Roku manufactured before may 2011 you
在2011年5月之前制造的Roku你
can visit cat5 TV / Roku to purchase a
可以访问cat5 TV / Roku购买
current generation system and continue
当前的发电系统并继续
to receive the best experience possible
尽可能获得最佳体验
from your Roku device the change will
从你的Roku设备改变
take effect on May thirtieth Robbie I
5月30日生效罗比一世
just have to say that this upsets me why
只是不得不说 这让我感到不安
it says to me because i own a purse from
它告诉我，因为我拥有一个钱包
10 years ago like I don't hurt it's an i
10年前我喜欢不伤害它
dumb purse right like so I don't want to
愚蠢的钱包就像这样我不想
buy I'm going to buy myself a rope I'm
买我打算给自己买一根 绳子
excited about it it's my birthday next
对此感到兴奋，这是我的下一个生日
month I'm buying myself a Roku it's 2015
一个月，我自己买了一个Roku，它是2015年
well I have to buy myself a new one in
好吧，我必须给自己买一个新的
2018 sighs I don't want that I can't
2018年叹息我不希望 我不能
take you seriously you just compared to
相比之下，你认真对待你
Roku to a purse but what I'm saying is
Roku到钱包但我说的是
that me and my consumer habits
我和我的消费习惯
I want things that i buy that I spend a
我想买的东西是 我花的
lot of money on to lie
很多钱要撒谎